[
  {
    "id": "353",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "What are the four EC2 options on AWS?",
      "answers": [
        "On demand instances",
        "Reserved instances",
        "Spot instances",
        "Dedicated host instances",
        "Physical instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["On demand instances", "Reserved instances", "Spot instances", "Dedicated host instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "354",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EC2 type of instance allows you to pay a fixed rate by the hour (or second for linux only) with no commitment?",
      "answers": [
        "On demand instances",
        "Reserved instances",
        "Spot instances",
        "Dedicated host instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["On demand instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "355",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EC2 type of instance provides you with a capacity reservation, and offers a significant discount on the hourly charge for an instance (has 1 and 3 year terms)?",
      "answers": [
        "On demand instances",
        "Reserved instances",
        "Spot instances",
        "Dedicated host instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Reserved instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "356",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EC2 type of instance enables you to bid whatever price you want for instance capacity, providing for even greater savings if your applications have flexible start and end times?",
      "answers": [
        "On demand instances",
        "Reserved instances",
        "Spot instances",
        "Dedicated host instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Spot instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "357",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EC2 type of instance are physical EC2 servers dedicated for your use, allowing you to use your existing server-bound software licenses (such as Oracle, VMWare, etc.)?",
      "answers": [
        "On demand instances",
        "Reserved instances",
        "Spot instances",
        "Dedicated host instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Dedicated host instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "358",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EC2 type of instance is for applications with short-term, spiky, or unpredictable workloads taht cannot be interrupted?",
      "answers": [
        "On demand instances",
        "Reserved instances",
        "Spot instances",
        "Dedicated host instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["On demand instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "359",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EC2 type of instance is for applications being deployed or tested for the first time?",
      "answers": [
        "On demand instances",
        "Reserved instances",
        "Spot instances",
        "Dedicated host instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["On demand instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "360",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EC2 type of instance is for applications that have a steady state or predictable usage?",
      "answers": [
        "On demand instances",
        "Reserved instances",
        "Spot instances",
        "Dedicated host instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Reserved instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "361",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EC2 type of instance is for applications that require reserved capacity?",
      "answers": [
        "On demand instances",
        "Reserved instances",
        "Spot instances",
        "Dedicated host instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Reserved instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "362",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EC2 type of instance gives the account owner the ability to make up-front payments to reduce the total computing cost of the EC2 instance?",
      "answers": [
        "On demand instances",
        "Reserved instances",
        "Spot instances",
        "Dedicated host instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Reserved instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "363",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "What are the three types of EC2 reserved instances?",
      "answers": [
        "Standard Reserved Instances",
        "Convertible Reserved Instances",
        "Scheduled Reserved Instances",
        "Special Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Standard Reserved Instances", "Convertible Reserved Instances", "Scheduled Reserved Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "364",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of reserved instance gives you up to 75% off when compared to on-demand?",
      "answers": [
        "Standard Reserved Instances",
        "Convertible Reserved Instances",
        "Scheduled Reserved Instances",
        "Special Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Standard Reserved Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "365",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of reserved instance gives you up to 45% off when compared to on-demand and the capability to change the attributes of the RI as long as the exchange results in the creation of RIs of equal or greater value?",
      "answers": [
        "Standard Reserved Instances",
        "Convertible Reserved Instances",
        "Scheduled Reserved Instances",
        "Special Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Convertible Reserved Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "366",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of reserved instance are available to launch within the time windows you reserve?",
      "answers": [
        "Standard Reserved Instances",
        "Convertible Reserved Instances",
        "Scheduled Reserved Instances",
        "Special Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Scheduled Reserved Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "367",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of reserved instance allows you to match your capacity reservation to a predictable recurring schedule that only requires a fraction of a day, week, or month?",
      "answers": [
        "Standard Reserved Instances",
        "Convertible Reserved Instances",
        "Scheduled Reserved Instances",
        "Special Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Scheduled Reserved Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "368",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of EC2 instance is useful for regulatory requirements that may not support multi-tenant virtualization?",
      "answers": [
        "On demand instances",
        "Reserved instances",
        "Spot instances",
        "Dedicated host instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Dedicated host instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "369",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of EC2 instance is useful for software licensing that does not support multi-tenancy or cloud deployments?",
      "answers": [
        "On demand instances",
        "Reserved instances",
        "Spot instances",
        "Dedicated host instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Dedicated host instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "370",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Which are true about EC2 Dedicated Host instances?",
      "answers": [
        "Can be purchased on-demand (hourly)",
        "Can be purchased as a reservation for up to 75% off the on-demand price",
        "Can be purchased for an indefinite period",
        "Can be purchased with the account owner as complete owner"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Can be purchased on-demand (hourly)", "Can be purchased as a reservation for up to 75% off the on-demand price"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "371",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the EC2 instance types is for dense storage, for example file servers or Data Warehousing, or Hadoop?",
      "answers": [
        "D2",
        "R4",
        "M4",
        "C4",
        "G2",
        "I2",
        "F1",
        "T2",
        "P2",
        "X1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["D2"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "372",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the EC2 instance types is for memory optimized workloads, for example memory intensive apps or Databases?",
      "answers": [
        "D2",
        "R4",
        "M4",
        "C4",
        "G2",
        "I2",
        "F1",
        "T2",
        "P2",
        "X1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["R4"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "373",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the EC2 instance types is for general purpose workloads, for example application servers?",
      "answers": [
        "D2",
        "R4",
        "M4",
        "C4",
        "G2",
        "I2",
        "F1",
        "T2",
        "P2",
        "X1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["M4"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "374",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the EC2 instance types is for compute optimized workloads, for example cpu intensive applications servers or Databases?",
      "answers": [
        "D2",
        "R4",
        "M4",
        "C4",
        "G2",
        "I2",
        "F1",
        "T2",
        "P2",
        "X1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["C4"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "375",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the EC2 instance types is for graphics intensive workloads, for example video encoding, 3D app streaming?",
      "answers": [
        "D2",
        "R4",
        "M4",
        "C4",
        "G2",
        "I2",
        "F1",
        "T2",
        "P2",
        "X1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["G2"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "376",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the EC2 instance types is for high speed storage workloads, for example NoSQL databases, data warehousing?",
      "answers": [
        "D2",
        "R4",
        "M4",
        "C4",
        "G2",
        "I2",
        "F1",
        "T2",
        "P2",
        "X1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["I2"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "377",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the EC2 instance types is for field programmable gate array workloads, for example hardware acceleration for your code?",
      "answers": [
        "D2",
        "R4",
        "M4",
        "C4",
        "G2",
        "I2",
        "F1",
        "T2",
        "P2",
        "X1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["F1"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "378",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the EC2 instance types is for lowest cost general purpose workloads, for example web servers, small databases?",
      "answers": [
        "D2",
        "R4",
        "M4",
        "C4",
        "G2",
        "I2",
        "F1",
        "T2",
        "P2",
        "X1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["T2"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "379",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the EC2 instance types is for graphics/general purpose GPU workloads, for example machine learning, bit coin mining?",
      "answers": [
        "D2",
        "R4",
        "M4",
        "C4",
        "G2",
        "I2",
        "F1",
        "T2",
        "P2",
        "X1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["P2"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "380",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the EC2 instance types is for memory optimized workloads, for SAP HANA, Apache Spark?",
      "answers": [
        "D2",
        "R4",
        "M4",
        "C4",
        "G2",
        "I2",
        "F1",
        "T2",
        "P2",
        "X1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["X1"]
    }
  }
]
